odownloadmanager.com 2016-10-27

# Open Download Manager :: Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

**Open Download Manager** and its Subsidiaries are committed to safeguarding your privacy online. This Privacy Policy discloses how we collect and use information, and the choices that you can make about the way we collect and use your information.

If you are under 18, you should ask your parents or a guardian before you use our Services. If you are not yet 18, do not use our Service; do not download our products.

#### Overview of Our Policy

**Open Download Manager** Website (We refer to our software and Products throughout this agreement as our "Services"). Please read this Terms & Conditions | Privacy Policy | Sitemap | About Us | Contact Us carefully so that you understand our online privacy practices regarding:

By accessing Sites, using our Services, providing information requested or by continuing to use our Services, you agree to accept the terms of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Sites or our Services.

We may make available shorter versions of this Privacy Policy. We also may supplement this policy for specific Services. Where there is a conflict between this policy and our summary or supplement, this policy will govern. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy. By accessing the sites or using the Services, you agree to be bound by this Terms & Conditions | Privacy Policy | Sitemap | About Us | Contact Us as modified.

#### Some Terms We Use in This Policy

Offers include e-mail, promotions, advertisements contests and third-party software presented by our Partners and us.

Personally Identifiable Information (PII) is any information that identifies or could be used to identify, contact or locate you. It also includes your credit card number.

Partner is an advertiser, or other entity with whom we have a business relationship to provide Offers.

Service FreeDownloads and Offers Site

Subsidiary is an entity wholly owned or related to **Open Download Manager**

User means an individual that has accessed the Sites on which we host our Products or Services.  
We and Our refer to Open Download Manager. and its subsidiaries.

You and Your refer to each user and his or her agents.

#### Personal Information We Collect

We may collect personal information at various times when you use our Services. Your participation is voluntary and you have the choice not to disclose any information that we request by choosing not to participate in an offer or exiting our Sites and Services.

Installation. During the installation process, we will present you with Offers. You may choose not to accept our Offers.

Contacts/IP Information. If you voluntarily submit information or Terms & Conditions | Privacy Policy | Sitemap | About Us | Contact Us (e.g. password request, technical support), we may keep a record of this communication. We do not merge this information with your Personally Identifiable Information.

#### Aggregate Information We Collect

When you use our Services, we may collect tracking information such as your IP address, browser type, the type of operating system you use, details about your computer hardware, the applications you have installed on your PC, the domain name of your Internet service provider, and pages you visited on our Sites. None of the information identifies you personally and we do not link aggregate information to Personally Identifiable Information.

Cookies. A cookie is a small text file sent to your browser. Cookies are stored on your computer's hard drive for record keeping purposes. We and our Partners use session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once you close your browser, the cookie will terminate. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's help file.

We use cookies to: 1) Remind us of who you are and to access your account information (stored on our computers). We also use cookies to store your zip code and other information you have submitted for other services, such as displaying your local weather; 2) Estimate our audience size. Each browser accessing our Services is given a unique cookie which is then used to determine the extent of repeat usage, usage by registered users and unregistered users, and to help target advertisements based on user interests; 3) Allow our Partners to track visits to their sites and stores. This information collected by cookies is sometimes called "clickstream" or "click trail" and may also describe which pages you have seen; 4) Measure certain traffic patterns, for example which of our Sites you have visited. We use this information to understand our users' habits so that we can make each new experience on a Site a better one.
